{
    "subject": "resource/Joseph_Stalin",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Honorary_Members_of_the_USSR_Academy_of_Sciences",
    "human_readable": "Joseph Stalin is the subject of Category:Honorary Members of the USSR Academy of Sciences.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9868292212486267,
            "question": "Was Joseph Stalin an Honorary Member of the USSR Academy of Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9673148989677429,
            "question": "In what historical period was Joseph Stalin an Honorary Member of the USSR Academy of Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9630416631698608,
            "question": "What criteria would have been necessary for Joseph Stalin to be considered for Honorary Membership in the USSR Academy of Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9177457094192505,
            "question": "What category does Joseph Stalin belong to in the context of the USSR Academy of Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8254718780517578,
            "question": "What does being an Honorary Member of the USSR Academy of Sciences signify?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7886233329772949,
            "question": "Are there other prominent individuals who hold the title of Honorary Members of the USSR Academy of Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.71470046043396,
            "question": "How does Joseph Stalin's membership in this category reflect his role in Soviet society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6649944186210632,
            "question": "Can you name a notable achievement or recognition associated with Joseph Stalin's membership in this category?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48091840744018555,
            "question": "What is the significance of the USSR Academy of Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39479294419288635,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other organizations or institutions that award honorary memberships?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joseph Stalin is the subject of Category:Honorary Members of the USSR Academy of Sciences.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4249_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the USSR Academy of Sciences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4249_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a notable achievement or recognition associated with Joseph Stalin's membership in this category?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4249_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Joseph Stalin's membership in this category reflect his role in Soviet society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4249_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4249_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my evaluation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is:\nJoseph Stalin is the subject of Category:Honorary Members of the USSR Academy of Sciences.\n\nFrom the provided context information, I found the following relevant points:\n\n* In file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4249/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt, it is mentioned that \"Membership document from 1939, showing Soviet leader Josef Stalin as a honorary member of the Academy of Sciences of the Soviet Union\".\n* In file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4249/re-ranker-msmarco/70.txt, it is mentioned that \"Joseph Stalin's certificate of an honorary member of the USSR Academy of Sciences\".\n\nBased on these points, I can confirm that Joseph Stalin is indeed a subject of Category:Honorary Members of the USSR Academy of Sciences.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided mention that Joseph Stalin received the title of honorary member of the USSR Academy of Sciences in 1939, which supports the statement that he is the subject of the Category:Honorary Members of the USSR Academy of Sciences."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}